sparkflow.net 2015-12-07

# Sparkflow - Privacy Policy

## Sparkflow Privacy Policy

Spark Flow LLC, (“Sparkflow” or “we”) respects the privacy of the visitors to our website located at www.sparkflow.net (the “Website”). We designed our privacy policy to make important disclosures about how we collect and use the information of visitors. We encourage you to read this policy. 

### Collection of Information on the Website

When you visit our Website, you can choose to provide us with certain personally identifiable information about yourself which may include your first and last name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, company name, date of birth, telephone number, billing and other personal information (“Personal Information”). We do not collect Personal Information from you unless you elect to provide it to us. We also collects other non-Personal Information on the Website which does not specifically identify you, including IP address, responses to questionnaires, browser type and device type. This data is used to manage and improve your experience on the Website and for any other business activities. We and third party service providers and our partners may use “cookies” and similar technology to customize your visit to the Website. Cookies are small text files that make it possible to store user-specific information on your personal device. Thereafter when you visit our Website, a message is sent back to the web server by the browser accessing our Website. It is also possible to use our Website without cookies. In your browser, you can deactivate the saving of cookies, limit them to particular websites, or set the browser to notify you when a cookie is sent. You can also delete cookies from the hard drive of your personal computer (folder: “cookies”) any time you want. However, not utilizing cookies may prevent you from using certain functions and features of our Websites. Data in cookies may be read to authenticate user sessions or provide services. We may use the information collected from the “cookies” to collect the pages visited, navigation patterns, etc. of a visitor. This information would help us learn things such as what product information or services is of most interest to our members, and what kinds of content our visitors like to see. 

### Collection of Information through the Sparkflow technologies

When you view and or interact with our technologies, we normally collect non-Personal Information such as ad consumption by time, interactions with the ad content, and the amount of ads you viewed or received. We may use the information internally for any lawful purpose. Additionally, we may share this information with our publishers and advertisers. It is important to note that the Personal Information is only collected through the Sparkflow technologies when you affirmatively elect to provide such information to a publisher/advertiser. 

### How we use your Personal Information

We will only use the Personal Information you provide under this policy in a manner that is consistent with this policy. If you have consented to receive promotional materials (e.g., newsletters) or notifications from us, we may periodically use your email address to send you such materials. If you want to stop receiving such materials from us, you can change your profile settings or follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

### How we secure your Personal Information

We are committed to ensuring the security of your personally identifiable information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, technical, and administrative measures, consistent with current technological and industry standards, to safeguard and secure the personally identifiable information we collect online. Without derogating from any disclaimers set forth under this policy, nothing under this Section or otherwise shall be deemed to imply an undertaking or duty of any sort by Sparkflow to securely or otherwise store, or prevent any loss of any and/or all data, results, information and/or any other materials obtained and/or stored through or in connection with the Software and Websites.
